// Questions for English
const QBANK_ENGLISH = [
  {
    prompt: "Giant pandas live in the bamboo forests of China.",
    options: ["verb", "preposition", "interjection", "adverb"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The beautiful waters of Tahiti attract swimmers and surfers from around the world.",
    options: ["preposition", "transitive verb", "helping verb", "coordinating conjunction"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Our teacher read aloud several poems by Countee Cullen.",
    options: ["action verb", "linking verb", "coordinating conjunction", "correlative conjunction"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you ever wonder where insects go during the winter?",
    options: ["verb", "preposition", "interjection", "linking verb"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Oh! You've cleaned the entire house!",
    options: ["adverb", "action verb", "interjection", "preposition"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "My favorite book is Inspirations: Stories About Women Artists.",
    options: ["linking verb", "coordinating conjunction", "preposition", "action verb"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Fascinated by the traditional Indian artwork, we carefully examined the yarn paintings.",
    options: ["transitive verb", "helping verb", "interjection", "adverb"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "My little sister wants to be either an astronaut or a ballerina.",
    options: ["adverb", "verb phrase", "correlative conjunction", "prepositional phrase"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "You should eat at least five servings of fruit and vegetables every day.",
    options: ["verb phrase", "prepositional phrase", "linking verb", "adverb"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Prem will teach us to play a form of volleyball that is popular in Thailand.",
    options: ["linking verb", "adverb", "helping verb", "coordinating conjunction"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Audible sounds",
    options: ["able to be heard", "very loud", "very irritating", "suddenly loud"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "A candid opinion",
    options: ["clever", "bad", "frank", "silly"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Conspicuous errors",
    options: ["often overlooked", "very serious", "easily seen", "sometimes hidden"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "To sing from the diaphragm",
    options: ["middle of stage", "muscles below chest cavity", "supporting structure", "third balcony of opera house"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Idle time",
    options: ["leisure", "winter", "historical", "hectic"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
];
